{
    "id": "49688a7b3e31453bb67b4e7d09d77e56",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My brotherâ€™s handwriting is ................................ mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worse than",
                "worse then",
                "worst than"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4f85d94e28e54f5e975daf75d1f94e23"
        },
        {
            "question": "Health is more important ................................. wealth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c362921af30443b2b264ebfcf59cb548"
        },
        {
            "question": "Blood is ................................ than water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thicker",
                "thickest",
                "more thick"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d793bf84a65841829228f795c239d9f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everest is .................................... peak in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "highest",
                "the highest",
                "higher"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2fb0d8af2fd1473d84fc507ec0f61f58"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ....................................... play that I have ever heard on the radio.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the more interesting",
                "the most interesting",
                "most interesting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0ef36c173ca40e9b46c036e446328e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie is ................................... beautiful of all the four sisters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the more",
                "the most",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "53667527fee2401995d59e1666a82672"
        },
        {
            "question": "The planet Mars is ......................................... from the earth than the satellite moon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "far",
                "farther",
                "farthest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "70afd2b8fb244834991d7d5a943107a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The elephant is ......................................... animal in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the large",
                "the largest",
                "the larger"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f6e029d59ce4d6286f27f23b832e56a"
        },
        {
            "question": "An ocean is certainly ......................................... than a sea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the bigger",
                "bigger",
                "big"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "29c65d371ead4f6b8718f633faf76a29"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am .......................................... interested in cricket than in football.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "most",
                "the more",
                "the most"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fcf8c12247074577b7d9e6af444e176b"
        }
    ]
}